Guide to the ILGWU. General Executive Board minutes, 1913-1995.
ILGWU. General Executive Board minutes,
- Series III. Executive Board Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1970-1995
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 5], 1984 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 5], 1984 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 6], 1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 6], 1985 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 6], 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 6], 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 6], 1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 6 of 6], 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 8], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 8], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 8], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 8], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 8], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 6 of 8], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 7 of 8], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 8 fo 8], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 9], 1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 9], 1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 9], 1988 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 9], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 9], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 6 of 9], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 7 of 9], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 8 of 9], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 9 of 9], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 6], 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 6], 1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 6], 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 6], 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 6], 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 6 of 6], 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 9], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 9], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 9], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 9], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 9], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 6 of 9], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 7 of 9], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 8 of 9], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 9 of 9], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 6], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 6], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 6], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 6], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 6], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 6 of 6], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 5], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 5], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 5], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 5], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 5], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 7], 1993 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 7], 1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Corresopndences. General. [folder 3 of 7], 1993 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 7], 1993 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 7], 1993 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 6 of 7], 1993 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 7 of 7], 1993 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 9], 1994 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 9], 1994 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 9], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 4 of 9], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 5 of 9], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 6 of 9], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 7 of 9], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 8 of 9], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 9 of 9], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1995 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Series IV. Committee Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1948-1978
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Appeals Committee. [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Appeals Committee. [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1978 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes. Campaign Committee., 1958-1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Minutes. Constitution Revision Committee., 1953 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Minutes. Education Committee. [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Minutes. Education Committee. [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Finance Committee., 1948-1975 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Minutes. Jurisdiction Committee., 1951-1954 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes. Local Managers' Committee. [folder 1 of 2], 1951-1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes. Local Managers' Committee. [folder 2 of 2], 1951-1972 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Personal Review Committee., 1964-1978 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Retirement Fund Committee. [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1976 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Retirement Fund Committee. [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1976 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Retiree Service Committee. [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1977 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Retiree Service Committee. [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1977 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Unity House Committee. [folder 1 of 2], 1955-1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Unity House Committee. [folder 2 of 2], 1955-1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Workers Benefits Committee. [folder 1 of 2], 1948-1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Workers Benefits Committee. [folder 2 of 2], 1948-1959 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Workers Benefits Committee. [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Reports and Correspondence. Workers Benefits Committee. [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)